## **NGUYEN VAN QUANG**

https://gitlab.com/vanquang2

## **ABOUT ME**

Highly motivated and enthusiastic Junior Software Development Engineer with more than 2 years of software engineering experience in the development of entire web apps and back-end services. I try to follow development trends and often learn new languages and technologies

In this year, in addition to development, I have led team of 5 people (1 Java developer, 1 IOS developer, 2 Backend developers and 1 QA).

In my free time I play computer games, improve my knowledge in English, and relax with Music

"Not complacent when praised n not narcissism when criticized"

## **CAREER GOALS**

I want to experience, learn a lot of knowledge, you know, because knowledge has no limit. So want to explore the world, new environment and challenge myself.

~ Work hard, living free!

## **EDUCATION**

BKACAD - Institute of Technology	08/2018 - 10/2021
Specialization: Software Developer; GPA: 2.92 (7.3/10.0)	
MINDX - Technology School	01/2020 - 05/2020
Specialization: Frontend Developer	

#### SKILLS

Programming Languages	PHP, Java, Javascript, Typescript
Frameworks & Libraries	Laravel, Yii2, Spring Boot, ReactJS, Flutter
Databases	Mysql, NoSql, Oracle
Service	GitLab, GitHub, Bitbucket, AWS
Development Tools	PHP Storm, Eclipse, Visual Studio Code, Android Studio
Language	English - above average

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Aladin Technology Company**

12/2021 - Now

Project Manager/ Tech Leader/ Software Developer

 Coway.com (Korea/Malaysia): E-commerce site has branches in many countries such as: Malaysia, Korea, Vietnam, US...

**Responsibilities : (Data Engineer)** Optimize oracle database, tune SQL to improve data query, use jennifer for traffic statistics and website usage

Technologies & Libraries: SpringBoot, Oracle

\_\_\_\_\_

• *BitelVideo (Viettel Peru)*: Provide solutions and plans to meet the user-friendliness of using the service. Solve the problem as well as develop more features for the website

Responsibilities: (Project Manager) Manage personnel and provide solutions directly with customers, participate in the development and (Software Developer) create new features that are not available according to customers' wishes to improve user experience. (Tech Leader) Architectural design; Implementation of high-level API used to create scripts for loading, processing and storing event data

Technologies & Libraries: PHP Yii2, Javacore, Mysql, Elasticsearch, Logstash, Redis

**Environment:** Centos, Nginx

• Imuzik.vn (Viettel Telecom): Imuzik is a free music listening platform, users can install a favorite song while waiting for a call.

**Responsibilities**: Work between client and IT department or developer team, work allocation, project schedule management. **(Software Developer)** Create module allowing users to listen to free music, register for services/download songs via text message

Technologies & Libraries: PHP Yii2, Mysql, Elasticsearch, Logstash, Redis

**Environment**: Centos, Nginx

#### Freelancer Bisto.vn

03/2021 - 08/2021

Software Developer

#### Responsibilities

- Developing e-commerce website on website/application platform. Wrote the API so that users can log in and shop, along with paying through formality Paypal/Visa
- Deploy the project to nginx, load balancer server
- Understanding how nginx ,elasticsearch works. Deploying small and medium projects with PHP technology

Technologies & Libraries: PHP Laravel 7.0, Mysql, Elasticsearch, Logstash

**Environment:** Windows Server, Apache

## **Department of state Documentary and Archives Vietnam**

09/2020 - 01/2021

IT Helpdesk

**Responsibilities**: Digital Transformation :using integrating digital technology into corporate and personal information management. Windows server system management and maintenance

Technologies & Libraries: Mysql, NoSql, Oracle

## **DESIRE**

I feel that I am lacking but I am also very enthusiastic about the information technology industry, not only in one area of the industry. So you know, i 've enough time and enthusiasm, cause im young

~ Work hard, living free!